Welcome to the Assessment Guide, module six, activity 2.3,
managing Technical and Legal Reports Part E.
In this assessment project,
you will be assessed on components of the following units.
There are three project activities you need to complete
as part of assessment Task two.
Read the scenario on the following page
before attempting the task.
The task must be completed in full
and the task is to be completed individually without
assistance from other participants.
These are resources you may use.
Before you attempt to do this assessment,
please read the declaration statement below.
Following is the scenario for this assessment,
read carefully and then later return to the scenario
to reference its components as it is full
of important information
and clues on how to complete the
assessment tasks successfully.
Use a step-by-step approach and check off completed tasks.
The time you spend reading
and fully understanding the scenario will
save you significant time.
When carrying out this assessment, you are required
to answer all questions on the answer sheet provided to you.
Ensure you complete all required information, refer
to your trainer for the due date of the assessment.
The rubric following is a great source of information
that will help you understand what is required
and how you will be marked.
Be sure to review the rubric for clues on what you need
to do to successfully complete the
tasks within the assessment.
The.